moneypantry.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy - MoneyPantry

## Effective Date: November, 2013

Here at MoneyPantry.com, we take your privacy seriously, just like we would like others to take our privacy seriously. That is why protecting your privacy is very important to us.

We hope the following information will help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us on MoneyPantry.com

The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of MoneyPantry.com ”we” or “us”). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using the MoneyPantry.com website (the “Site”), and the ways in which we use this information. This Privacy Policy, including our children’s privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail).

**Please read this Privacy Policy carefully**  
By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we’ll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

MoneyPantry.com strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. “Period.”

**How We Collect and Use Email Addresses and Other Personally Identifiable Information**  
Like many websites, MoneyPantry.com offers users the ability to sign up for an email newsletter. Your email is held within a trusted email service provider (Aweber Inc). You can unsubscribe from email communications at any time using the email service provider’s “unsubscribe” button. You can also email satrap (at) MoneyPantry (dot) com if you’d prefer to be manually removed from the email list.

We will occasionally email you about, new content and special events happening with the MoneyPantry community. Your email is never rented, sold, or shared with any 3rd party.

If you have questions about how we manage your email address and other personally identifiable information, feel free to contact

satrap (at) moneypantry (dot) com

**Or send a letter to:**  
Saeed Darabi  
120 Humes Ln  
Florissant, MO 63031  
USA

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**How We Gather Information from Users**  
How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in surveys, sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site.

Like most Web sites, MoneyPantry.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site.

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

**Google Analytics Tracking**  
We’ve implemented a tracking code in order to collect demographic information in Google Anayltics.

You can opt-out of this program anytime by adjusting your [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). You may also wish to review other [available opt-outs](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**What we do with the information we collect**

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually. Although we use remarketing, we don’t collect or store personally identifiable information, including demographic information. We also don’t send Google any precise information (ie. location) without your consent. In terms of Remarketing, Google reserves the right to display to users which remarketing lists they’re on, along with the corresponding domain name.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on MoneyPantry.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by MoneyPantry.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by MoneyPantry.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers & Links.” This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. [See the “Third Party Advertisers” section.]

**Third Party Advertisers Links and Affiliated Sites**  
MoneyPantry.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on MoneyPantry.com pages, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through MoneyPantry.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, surveys, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties MoneyPantry.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

Our websites contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each website to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information.

While we may use cookies in some parts of our website, cookies received with advertisements on our website are collected by the respective advertising companies, and we do not possess access to or control of such information gathered.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

**Specific Parties**  
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**Children’s Privacy Statement Based on COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**  
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

This children’s privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.

This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site.

Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site.

Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we do NOT condition the participation of a child under thirteen in the Site’s online activities on providing personally identifiable information.

_We can be reached by contacting:_  
Email: satrap –at– MoneyPantry (dot) com

**Fair Information Practices**  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via in site notification  
• Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**  
We collect your email address in order to:  
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:  
• NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses  
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way  
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters  
• Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly  
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can  
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**  
[CalOPPA](http://consumercal.org/about-cfc/cfc-education-foundation/what-should-i-know-about-privacy-policies/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/) is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy.

According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

**Governing law**  
This policy and the use of these Sites are governed by Missouri law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Missouri. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration at the following location: Missouri, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

MoneyPantry.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within Missouri. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

**Changes to this Policy**  
MoneyPantry.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

**Your Rights**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing us or by postal mail. In protection of the privacy of yourself and others, we may have to acquire identification evidence before we can allow you to access to information regarding you in order to retrieve or change it.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Saaed Darabi  
120 Humes Ln  
Florissant, Missouri 63031  
United States  
satrap (at) moneypantry (.) com
